http://neohgolf.com/privacy-policy/

Who we areNortheast Ohio Golf is a Cleveland Creative Inc. property. Our website address is: https://neohgolf.com.Personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact FormsNortheast Ohio Golf uses a contact form for email newsletter registration. If you have subscribed to our newsletter or if you are a member of our website (i.e. you can log in through an account you created) or if you have purchased something on our website, there is a good chance you will receive emails from us.We will only send you emails which you have signed up to receive, or which pertain to the services we provided to you.To send you emails, we use the name and email address you provide us. Our site also logs the IP address you used when you signed up for the service to prevent abuse of the system.No identifiable information is otherwise tracked outside this website except for the email address.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsNEOHgolf.com uses a standard version of Google Analytics to track user visits and page view information. For details on the privacy policies related to Google Analytics, see Google’s privacy statements here.Who we share your data withNortheast Ohio Golf does not directly share data with anyone. We may contact you through our systems on behalf of a partner or advertiser, but we do not provide them with our user data.Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that ACCOUNT SIGN UP on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Contact informationNortheast Ohio Golf Cleveland Creative Inc. 8069 Amber Lane Brecksville OH 44141216-577-8756 golf@neohgolf.com
Facebook
LinkedIn
Twitter
MENUHomeTournament CalendarsTournament CalendarJunior CalendarCharity CalendarCourse DirectoryAssociationsAkron District Golf AssnChippewa Scratch LeagueCleveland Metroparks GolfFox Den Big Skins GameGolfweek Amateur TourGreater Cleveland Skins GameIndependent TournamentsNEOH.GOLF Tournament SeriesNorth Coast Junior TourNorthern Ohio Golf AssnNorthern Ohio PGANOPGA Junior GolfUSGAMore Site SectionsGHIN in Northeast Ohio: Join the NEOH.GOLF Club!NEOH Golf NewsGolf Jobs BoardNEOH High School GolfNEOH Junior GolfGolf Life NEOHAdvertise HereEmail Newsletter Back
Search for:
